[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these methods is the best for planting a peach tree?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Planting should be north-south when the trees are planted in rows.", "Trees should be fully exposed to the sunlight and a free air flow.", "The best time for planting peach trees is early winter."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carl Cody is captured in what facility at LAX, and what does he claim his profession to be?", "correct_answer": "In a Mens room at the airport, a businessman", "incorrect_answers": ["In a bar at the airport, a bartender", "On nearby Century Blvd., a male temptress", "Cargo City section of the airport, a ramp services personnel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What goes along with love according to a Frank Sinatra hit song?", "correct_answer": "Marriage", "incorrect_answers": ["Broken hearts", "Pain", "Sex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, The African Queen, Charlie is American by birth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Woody Allens movie Sleeper, a small pyramid statue is used by several party-goers as a sort of inebriator or mind altering device.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy there are several references to a super-intelligent shade of the color blue, called this.", "correct_answer": "Hooloovoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyan", "Volo-loco", "Gobo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the hugely popular International Movie Data Base web site (imdb.com), members rated this Number 3 AFI Top Ten movie as Number 1 of the sites Top 250 Movies of All Time.", "correct_answer": "The Godfather", "incorrect_answers": ["Plan 9 from Outer Space", "Star Wars (1977)", "The Shawshank Redemption"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1958, Pope Pius XII designated an Italian saint as the patron saint for television.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first space station?", "correct_answer": "Salyut", "incorrect_answers": ["MIR", "Soyuz", "Skylab 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a ridge of coral in the sea called?", "correct_answer": "Coral Reef", "incorrect_answers": ["Atoll", "None of these", "Coral Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Samuel Coleridges longest poem which contains the lines:\nThe moving Moon went up the sky.\nAnd nowhere did abide.", "correct_answer": "The Rime of the Ancient Mariner", "incorrect_answers": ["Kubla Khan", "A Vision in a Dream", "The Pains of Sleep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the staples of the Rambo franchise is the obligatory sequence of guerrilla warfare carnage. In which movie does the guerrilla carnage take place in an underground cave?", "correct_answer": "Rambo III", "incorrect_answers": ["Rambo", "First Blood", "First Blood Part II"]}]